Don Walker Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 28-131)
  - Non-Show Music (Box 92-106, 127-131)
    - College songs
      - Agnes de Mille Dance Theatre, circa 1953, Unless otherwise noted, the folders below contain a full score, piano-conductor score, and string parts; some of the full scores appear to be in the hand of Hans Spialek
        - Parvenus (Box-folder 96/4)
        - Pavane, Violin parts (Box-folder 96/5)
        - Stage fright (Box-folder 96/6)
        - Transition after ballet class (Box-folder 96/7)
        - Transition after stage fright (Box-folder 96/8)
        - Transition to gala performance (Box-folder 96/9)
        - Waltz ballet (Box-folder 96/10)
        - Wheels (Great Pacific railway) (Box-folder 96/11)
      - Dear old us coda, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 96/12)
      - Debussy preludes #3, Arranged by Don Walker
        - I. General Lavine
          - Full score (Box-folder 127/2)
          - Parts (Box-folder 96/13)
        - II. La fille aux cevaux de lin
          - Full score (Box-folder 127/3)
          - Parts (Box-folder 96/14)
        - III. Minstrels
          - Full score (Box-folder 127/4)
          - Parts (Box-folder 96/15)
      - Debussy preludes #4
        - IV. Reverie
          - Full score (Box-folder 127/5)
          - Parts (Box-folder 96/16)
      - Design for loving, Sketch, lead sheet; Incomplete (Box-folder 97/1)
      - Dinah, Short score (Box-folder 97/2)
      - Doin' the New York, Sketch (Box-folder 97/3)
      - Down with love, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 97/4)
      - Drinking song, Vocal arrangement, short score (Box-folder 97/5)
      - Dubinsky, Matt see Songs with Matt Dubinsky
      - Dust on the moon, Parts; Published arrangement by Don Walker (Box-folder 97/6)
      - An early spring, Piano score, lead sheet; Lyrics by Don Walker (Box-folder 97/7)
      - Easy does it, Piano score (Box-folder 97/8)
      - Everglades, Full score (Box-folder 97/9)
      - Fall into somebody's arms, Piano-vocal score, lyric sheets (Box-folder 97/10)
      - Farewell blues, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 97/11)
      - Songs by Brian Foley, Lead sheets; Titles include: Half of me; I belong to the road; If I had today; I’m looking for someone; Success, you haven’t spoiled me yet; Woman with child (Box-folder 97/12)
      - Footsore blues, Lead sheet (Box-folder 97/13)
      - For once and for always, Lead sheet; No lyric (Box-folder 97/14)
      - Forbidden love, Lead sheet; Lyrics by Don Walker (Box-folder 97/15)
      - Forget-me-not, Piano-vocal score; By Don Walker, Bix Reichner, David Zoob (Box-folder 97/16)
      - The fourth of July march, Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 97/17)
      - From the garden of Kama, Parts (Box-folder 97/18)
      - Funny little sailor man, Full score; From The new moon (Box-folder 97/19)
      - G.E. time, Piano-vocal score; No lyric (Box-folder 97/20)
      - Geisha, Sketch (Box-folder 97/21)
      - Gigot-one step, Piano score (Box-folder 97/22)
      - Glad singers, Includes scores for albums “Surprise!” (Columbia CL 2312/CS 9112) and “The Glad Singers Swing Bells!: Christmas with a beat” (Columbia CL 2391/CS 9191), arranged by Don Walker and Arnold Goland, conducted by Hal Hastings; Most folders below include full scores (primarily rhythm sections), and piano-conductor scores with vocal arrangement, a separate vocal arrangement, and in some cases parts
        - After midnight (Box-folder 127/6)
        - Between the dances (Box-folder 127/7)
        - Don't let the neighbors know (Box-folder 127/8)
        - F'nick (Box-folder 127/9)
        - Far from the home I love (Box-folder 127/10)
        - For you (Box-folder 127/11)
        - Fum, fum, fum (Box-folder 127/12)
        - Gloria (Box-folder 127/13)
        - God rest ye merry, gentlemen (Box-folder 127/14)
        - Good King Wenceslaus (Box-folder 127/15)
        - Happy new year (Box-folder 128/1)
        - Hark the herald angels sing (Box-folder 128/2)
        - I love you truly (Box-folder 128/3)
        - Joy! (Box-folder 128/4)
        - Loveline (Box-folder 128/5)
        - Mazeltov (Box-folder 128/6)
        - Now I have everything (Box-folder 128/7)
        - One more range (Box-folder 128/8)
        - Ox and donkey (Box-folder 128/9)
        - Perfect day (Box-folder 128/10)
        - Russian lullaby (Box-folder 128/11)
        - Surprise! (Box-folder 97/23)
        - There once was a man (Box-folder 128/12)
        - Three kings (Box-folder 128/13)
        - Tokyo medley (Box-folder 128/14)
        - Where the blue of the night (Box-folder 128/15)
        - You're too sure of me, p. 1 of full score only (Box-folder 128/16)
      - Lyrics and notes (Box-folder 97/24)
      - Miscellaneous music (Box-folder 97/25)
      - Great day, Prelude to great day, Sketches (Box-folder 97/26)
      - Green briars, Lead sheet; Lyrics by Don Walker (Box-folder 97/27)
      - Grenadiers, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 97/28)
      - Growin' pains, Published parts; Music and lyrics by Don Walker and Clay Warnick (Box-folder 97/29)
      - Ray Hartley (pianist), Includes scores for album “For Lovers” (RCA Victor LPM/LSP 1870), arranged and conducted by Don Walker ( 1959 )
        - Autumn in Rome
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/1)
          - Short scores (Box-folder 98/1)
        - A better word than love
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/2)
          - Short score, piano-conductor score with vocals, vocal arrangement (Box-folder 98/2)
        - Beyond the purple hills
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/3)
          - Short scores (Box-folder 98/3)
        - A certain smile
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/4)
          - Short scores (Box-folder 98/4)
        - Come love me
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/5)
          - Short score (Box-folder 98/5)
        - Friendly persuasion (thee I love)
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/6)
          - Short score (Box-folder 98/6)
        - A handful of stars
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/7)
          - Short score (Box-folder 98/7)
        - Heart of Paris
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/8)
          - Short scores with vocals, vocal arrangement (Box-folder 98/8)
        - I remember it well
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/9)
          - Short scores (Box-folder 98/9)
        - Intermezzo
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/10)
          - Short scores (Box-folder 98/10)
        - Music from another world
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/11)
          - Short score with vocals, vocal arrangement (Box-folder 98/11)
        - Secret love
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/12)
          - Short score with vocals, vocal arrangement (Box-folder 98/12)
        - Shadow of love
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/13)
          - Short scores (Box-folder 98/13)
        - Speak low
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/14)
          - Short score (Box-folder 98/14)
        - Tenderly
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/15)
          - Short score with vocals, vocal arrangement (Box-folder 98/15)
        - They can't take that away from me
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/16)
          - Short score (Box-folder 98/16)
        - To each his own
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/17)
          - Short score (Box-folder 98/17)
        - A very precious love
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/18)
          - Short score (Box-folder 98/18)
        - When I grow too old to dream
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/19)
          - Short score with vocals (Box-folder 98/19)
        - Whispers in the wind
          - Full score (Box-folder 129/20)
          - Short score with vocals, vocal arrangement (Box-folder 98/20)
        - Havana, Full score (Box-folder 130/2)
        - Heat wave, Sketch (Box-folder 98/21)
        - Highway medley, Short score (Box-folder 98/22)
        - Honeymoon madrigal, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 98/23)
        - Humming, Full score, piano-vocal score (Box-folder 130/3)
        - Humoresque stomp!, Full score; On title page: Walker and Cohan opus #1 (Box-folder 98/24)
        - Hungarian dance no. V and VI, Piano score/condensed score (Box-folder 98/25)
        - I can't make my heart behave
          - Full score (Box-folder 98/26)
          - Lead sheet (Box-folder 98/27)
          - Parts (Box-folder 98/28)
        - I go home to baby, Piano-vocal score, lyric sheet; Incomplete (Box-folder 98/29)
        - I gotta snek!, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 98/30)
        - If I can't have you (I want to be lonesome-I want to be blue), Piano-vocal score/short score; Notes on verso (Box-folder 98/31)
        - If you didn't belong to me, Lead sheet (Box-folder 98/32)
        - If this isn't love, Full score (Box-folder 129/21)
        - I'll go my way, Full score (Box-folder 129/22)
        - I'll share it all with you/dance chorus, Piano score with choreographic notes (Box-folder 98/33)
        - I'm a big girl now, Lead sheet (Box-folder 98/34)
        - I'm glad there is you, Piano-conductor score/parts; For Martha Wright (Box-folder 98/35)
        - I'm gonna worry, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 99/1)
        - I'm ready, Piano-vocal scores; Lyrics by Don Walker (Box-folder 99/2)
        - In one easy lesson, Lead sheet (Box-folder 99/3)
        - Indian rhapsody, Full score; Incomplete; Laid in: short score/sketch (Box-folder 99/4)
        - Ink spots, Piano score (Box-folder 99/5)
        - Into the night, Piano score, piano-vocal score; Music by Don Walker (Box-folder 99/6)
        - The intruder, 4 piano-vocal scores, lyric sheet; Music by Don Walker, lyrics by Jack Lawrence (Box-folder 99/7)
        - Invictus, Short score (Box-folder 99/8)
        - Is it love? 's' must be love, Piano-vocal score; By Don Walker and David Zoob; Fragile, torn and bent (Box-folder 99/9)
        - I've found what I wanted, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 99/10)
        - I've got rhythm, Sketch (Box-folder 99/11)
        - Just a whistlin' and a whittlin', Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 99/12)
        - Kamenoi-ostrow, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 99/13)
        - Kashmiri song, Parts, including piano-conductor (Box-folder 99/14)
        - Kiss me again/Ah sweet mystery of life/A kiss in the dark, Sketch for arrangement (Box-folder 99/15)
        - Lady play your mandolin, Short score (Box-folder 99/16)
        - The last round-up, Full score/piano-conductor score (Box-folder 99/17)
        - Let music ring, Condensed score/sketch (Box-folder 99/18)
        - Let's go too far, Published parts; Music and lyrics by Don Walker and Clay Warnick (Box-folder 99/19)
        - Liebestraum, Short score/sketches (Box-folder 99/20)
        - Lime house blues, Score (Box-folder 99/21)
        - Lindencroft Music, Music by Don Walker
          - Nocturne; Coda to nocturne, Piano score (Box-folder 99/22)
          - Quartet, Score (Box-folder 99/23)
          - Rondo and nocturne, Score (Box-folder 99/24)
          - Rondo and nocturne, String parts; Violin part missing (Box-folder 99/25)
          - Trio, Sketch (Box-folder 99/26)
        - Lonely little Cinderella, Published parts; Arranged by Don Walker (Box-folder 99/27)
        - Louise, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 99/28)
        - Louisiana hayride, Short score/sketch, may be a vocal arrangement (Box-folder 99/29)
        - Love for sale
          - Full score (Box-folder 130/4)
          - Parts (Box-folder 100/1)
        - Love in bloom, Short score/sketches (Box-folder 100/2)
        - Love is the funniest thing, Piano-vocal score/sketch, lyric sheets (Box-folder 100/3)
        - Love nest medley, Full score (Box-folder 100/4)
        - Lover come back to me, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 100/5)
        - Lower solebury lurch, Piano score (Box-folder 100/6)
        - Lullaby land, Piano-vocal score; No lyric (Box-folder 100/7)
        - The lure of l'amour, Piano-vocal score, lyric sheet (Box-folder 100/8)
        - Lush, Sketch (Box-folder 100/9)
        - M.S.W. finale gripe, Piano score (Box-folder 100/10)
        - Mad Hatter and Alice/Alice incidental, Sketches (Box-folder 100/11)
        - The magic highway, Piano-vocal scores; Music and lyrics by Don Walker and Fred Culley (Box-folder 100/12)
        - Maine, Sketch (Box-folder 100/13)
        - Manhattan, Piano-vocal score/sketch; By Don Walker (Box-folder 100/14)
        - Manhattan serenade, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 100/15)
        - Marche ecossaise, Percussion and oboe II parts (Box-folder 100/16)
        - Marches based on the themes from "The Turks in Italy", Lead sheet (Box-folder 100/17)
        - Marie
          - Full score (Box-folder 130/6)
          - Parts (Box-folder 100/18)
        - May-night, Full score (Box-folder 100/19)
        - Mighty lak' a rose, Piano score/condensed score (Box-folder 100/20)
        - Minute waltz, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 100/21)
        - Mississippi (a tone journey), Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 100/22)
        - Moanin' low, Short score (Box-folder 100/23)
        - Modulations, Sketches (Box-folder 100/24)
        - The most happy fella: symphonic impressions
          - Full score (Box-folder 100/25)
          - Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 100/26)
          - Incomplete parts (Box-folder 100/27)
        - Mr. and Mrs. America, Full score, vocal arrangement (Box-folder 101/1)
        - Music in the air, Short score/sketches (Box-folder 101/2)
        - Musical ideas for songs vol. 1, Notebook of sketches, piano-vocal scores, piano scores and lyrics; some incomplete; Titles include: Child of love; Believe it or not; Where did you learn to love?; Close to my heart; Nature does great things; Anything you say/Willing; I don’t like your family; Breakfast in bed; A five year plan (for two); Jig-saw; Turn up your nose to the blues; Far away; The little red book; What is it all about?; If you’re really in love with me; You are all the world to me; In a house up on a hill; 16 bar thing; Beguine (Box-folder 101/3)
        - My land my music, Short score with vocals, piano-vocal score; Music by Don Walker, lyrics by Bickley Reichner (Box-folder 101/4)
        - My love was young, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 101/5)
        - My new Kentucky home, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 101/6)
        - My shawl, Published parts; Arranged by Don Walker (Box-folder 101/7)
        - Mysterioso, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 101/8)
        - The navy march, Short score; Titles include: The Navy blue and gold; The Navy hymn; Anchors aweigh (Box-folder 101/9)
        - Never looked so high, Piano-vocal score, lyric sheet (Box-folder 101/10)
        - Night and day
          - Full score, Appears to be by Lee Armonel for Waring's Pennsylvanians (Box-folder 101/11)
          - Lead sheet (Box-folder 101/12)
        - Nina Rosa selection #2, Short score, sketch (Box-folder 101/13)
        - Nola, Short score (Box-folder 101/14)
        - Not so far, Sketch (Box-folder 101/15)
        - October suite, Music by Don Walker
          - Birthday song I, Short score (Box-folder 101/16)
          - Grey day, Piano score/sketch (Box-folder 101/17)
        - Oh Marie, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 101/18)
        - Old fashioned walking music; Old fashioned intro, Sketches (Box-folder 101/19)
        - Old love/no love, Piano-vocal score, lyric sheets (Box-folder 101/20)
        - Old man river, Full score; Portions torn away (Box-folder 101/21)
        - Old playmate, Short score (Box-folder 101/22)
        - Once upon a time, Short score (Box-folder 101/23)
        - One step stuff, One step chorus, Sketches (Box-folder 101/24)
        - Opening, Sketch (Box-folder 101/25)
        - Oriental suite, Piano-vocal scores; By Don Walker
          - Climbin' up K2 (Box-folder 101/26)
          - Field of cement (Box-folder 101/27)
          - Lotus and the wind (Box-folder 102/1)
          - A stamp from Tanna Tuva (Box-folder 102/2)
          - We met in Samarkand (Box-folder 102/3)
        - Our kind of love, Piano-vocal score, lyric sheet, correspondence (Box-folder 102/4)
        - Outside of you, Full score (Box-folder 130/6)
        - La paloma, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 102/5)
        - Paradise lane, Piano-vocal score; Music and lyrics by Don Walker (Box-folder 102/6)
        - Paris in the spring, Full score (Box-folder 130/7)
        - Paso doble, Sketch (Box-folder 102/7)
        - Selections from Patience, Full score (Box-folder 130/8)
        - Pepe's theme, Piano-vocal score; No lyric (Box-folder 102/8)
        - The perfume of the burning leaves, Sketch (Box-folder 102/9)
        - Piccolo Pete, Sketch (Box-folder 102/10)
        - A picture of me without you, Sketch, lyric sheets (Box-folder 102/11)
        - Pity, Short scores (Box-folder 102/12)
        - The powder room song, Lead sheet (Box-folder 102/13)
        - Princess Flavia duet Act II, Sketch; Title is crossed out and music may be unrelated (Box-folder 102/14)
        - Professor hot, Piano-vocal score, sketch (Box-folder 102/15)
        - Ranger's song, Short score; Incomplete (Box-folder 102/16)
        - The relief of Lucknow, Sketch (Box-folder 102/17)
        - Revolutionary ballet, Full score, negative photostat; Incomplete (Box-folder 102/18)
        - The riff song, Full score, piano-vocal score (Box-folder 102/19)
        - The ringing rocks, Piano scores (Box-folder 102/20)
        - Rittman study material
          - Methods of melodic development (of basic theme), Score and notes (Box-folder 102/21)
          - Miscellaneous music, Sketches (Box-folder 102/22)
          - Miscellaneous notes (Box-folder 102/23)
        - The rogue song, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 102/24)
        - Romberg medley #9, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 102/25)
        - Sigmund Romberg, The following scores came with materials that indicated that they were used for the concert “An Evening with Sigmund Romberg and his Concert Orchestra” at Carnegie Hall, 1949 May 1, similar concerts in 1945, and various other concerts and recording projects which featured music by Romberg.
          - American humoresque, Full score (Box-folder 102/26)
          - Blow Gabriel blow, Vocal arrangement with short score (Box-folder 102/27)
          - Blue heaven, Full score; Possible Romberg holograph; originally attached to "One kiss" full score (Box-folder 102/28)
          - Czech medley arranged for Novotna, Short scores; Includes Romberg holograph; Titles include: The quest (Nestuůjte mladenci); Kdo ma pocerucc Galanku (Box-folder 102/29)
          - Deep in my heart, dear, Full score and short score (Box-folder 102/30)
          - The donkey serenade, Short score/full score (Box-folder 102/31)
          - Faithfully yours, Full score (Box-folder 129/23)
          - Fantasia, Negative photostat of full score (Box-folder 131/1)
          - The firemen's bride from Up in Central Park, Full score; Described as Victor recording arrangement (Box-folder 103/1)
          - Funny little sailor men, Piano-vocal score/vocal arrangement (Box-folder 103/2)
          - Girl on the prow see also Romberg medley #8 continued, Short score (Box-folder 103/3)
          - Golden days from The student prince, Full score; Upper left corner torn away (Box-folder 129/24)
          - A horn in the fiddle shop, Full score (Box-folder 103/4)
          - Military march from Desert song, Full score; Possible Romberg holograph (Box-folder 103/5)
          - My Maryland (selection), Full score; Possible Romberg holograph (Box-folder 129/25)
          - New moon-selection #2, Notes (Box-folder 103/6)
          - One alone, Full score (Box-folder 131/2)
          - One alone, Vocal arrangement and short score (Box-folder 103/7)
          - One kiss, Full score, short score, lead sheet; First line of lead sheet appears to be Romberg holograph; segues to “Blue heaven” which was initially attached to full score (Box-folder 103/8)
          - One kiss, String parts (Box-folder 103/9)
          - Riff song, Full score; Possible Romberg holograph (Box-folder 129/26)
          - Romance, Full score; Possible Romberg holograph (Box-folder 129/27)
          - Romberg medley #2, Short score (Box-folder 103/10)
          - Romberg medley #8 continued, Full score; Possible Romberg holograph; Primarily of "Girl on the prow" (Box-folder 103/11)
          - Serenade from The student prince, Piano-vocal score/vocal arrangement (Box-folder 103/12)
          - Softly, as in a morning sunrise, Full score, short score, vocal arrangement (2); Full score possible Romberg holograph (Box-folder 103/13)
          - Stouthearted man, Full score; Possible Romberg holograph (Box-folder 103/14)
          - Sweethearts from Maytime, Full score; Possible Romberg holograph; Laid in: reverse parts for violin and viola (Box-folder 103/15)
          - Swift theme, Piano score (Box-folder 103/16)
          - Tirolian woodchoppers march, Full score; Possible Romberg holgraph (Box-folder 103/17)
          - Tirolian woodchoppers march, Vocal parts (Box-folder 103/18)
          - Tirolian woodchoppers march, Parts (Box-folder 103/19-20)
          - Tirolean yoodler's, Vocal arrangement, vocal parts (Box-folder 103/21)
          - Up in Central Park, Piano-vocal scores or piano scores; Titles include: April snow, Barry specialty, Finale ultimo, Finaletto scene 4 act II, Fireman’s bride, The reprise, Incidental and change of scene, Opening Act I, Opening scene 3 Act I, When you walk in the room (Box-folder 104/1)
          - Viennese nights-waltzes, Full score (Box-folder 104/2)
          - When I grow too old to dream, Full score, short score, vocal arrangement; Full score possible Romberg holograph (Box-folder 104/3)
          - Miscellaneous unidentified music, Sketches (Box-folder 104/4)
          - Miscellaneous photostat negatives, Full scores; Includes Moods of Tecla part II-IV (Box-folder 104/5)
        - The rosary, Piano-vocal score/vocal arrangement (Box-folder 104/6)
        - Running to mother, Full score (Box-folder 104/7)
        - Running to mother, Parts (Box-folder 104/8)
        - Samba, Short score (Box-folder 104/9)
        - Scandals medley, Full score, short score/sketch; Titles include: This is the missus; Life is just a bowl of cherries (Box-folder 104/10)
        - September in the rain, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 104/11)
        - Serenade, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 104/12)
        - Serenade for a wealthy widow, Piano-vocal score/piano score (Box-folder 104/13)
        - She's happy now with him, Piano-vocal score; Music by Don Walker, lyrics by Bix Reichner (Box-folder 104/14)
        - Selections from Show boat, Full score (Box-folder 104/15)
        - Selections from Show boat, Short score (Box-folder 104/16)
        - Sittin' around on Sunday, Full score (Box-folder 131/3)
        - 6/8 chorus, Piano-vocal score; No lyric (Box-folder 104/17)
        - Smoke rings, Parts (Box-folder 104/18)
        - Snow Queen adagio, Short score (Box-folder 104/19)
        - So long, Piano-vocal score; Incomplete (Box-folder 104/20)
        - Soda jerker, Piano-vocal score; No lyric (Box-folder 104/21)
        - Softly, as in a morning sunrise, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 104/22)
        - Somebody else took you out of my arms (but I can't take you out of my dreams), Piano-vocal score; No lyric (Box-folder 104/23)
        - Song of Norway-selection, Full score (Box-folder 104/24)
        - Song of the Bayou/Anytime's the time to fall in love, Piano score/piano-vocal score (Box-folder 104/25)
        - Songs with Matt Dubinsky, Piano-vocal scores and lyric sheets; Music by Don Walker
          - Dear angel child, Appears to have been for a show titled Eight cousins (Box-folder 104/26)
          - Is this what love is? (Box-folder 105/1)
          - Never love a stranger (Box-folder 105/2)
          - Spooks! (Box-folder 105/3)
          - You'll see (Box-folder 105/4)